Guide to the Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records, 1893-2008.
Cornell University Department of Theatre Arts records
- Series IV. Cornell University Theatre and Cornell Dramatic Club
  - Programs, Posters and other Printed Materials
    - Regular and Summer Season Programs
      - 1937-1938 Season
        - 1937 Forbes Heermans Prize Plays (And May God Have Mercy; Spring; Art and Appreciation), March 18-19, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
        - Four British Prize Plays (Arising Out of the Minutes; Folly of Faith; Tails Up; "Come Away, Death!"), April 15-16, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
        - Heartbreak House, April 29-30, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
        - The Breadwinner, May 6-7, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
        - 1938 Heermans Plays (Farmer's Holiday; Vigil; ...and the Pursuit of Happiness; Great Caesar!? A Skit, May 14, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
        - Aaron Slick from Punkin Crick, May 20-21, 27-28, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
        - Beano, May 30, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
        - First Lady, June 17-18, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 42)
      - Summer 1938
        - Heartbreak House, July 8-9, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 43)
        - Uncle Vanya, July 15-16, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 43)
        - Aaron Slick from Punkin Crick, July 22-23, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 43)
        - Variety Night (The Fall of the City; And the Pursuit of Happiness; Miriam McCollom; A Seat in the Park; Housebreak Vanya; The Aaron Slick Quartette; Miriam McCollom; Great Caesar!?), July 29-30, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 43)
        - The Yellow Jacket, August 5-6, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 43)
        - Private Lives, August 10-11, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 43)
      - 1938-1939 Season (30th)
        - The Breadwinner, October 22, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - The Yellow Jacket, November 4-5, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - Among the Breakers, November 12, 18-19, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - It Can't Happen Here, December 16-17, 1938 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - Excursion, January 14, 20-21, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - Tovarich, February 10-11, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - Four One-Act Comedies (Be Sure Your Sex Will Find You Out; Why I Am a Bachelor; Tickless Time; Privilege and Privation), March 25, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - Three New York State Plays (Apartment 3D; Let's Get on with the Marryin'; A Day in the Vineyard), April 21-22, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 44)
        - The Cardiff Giant, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 44)
          Includes May 20, 26-27 and June 15-17
      - Summer 1939
        - It Can't Happen Here, July 7-8, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 45)
        - The Three Sisters, July 14-15, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 45)
        - Four Original One-Act Plays on New York State Themes (A Little House in Angelica; Family Co-operative; A Day in the Vineyard; Mixing Up the Rent), July 21-22, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 45)
        - Excursion, July 28-29, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 45)
        - Cardiff Giant, August 4-5, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 45)
        - Candida, August 9-10, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 45)
      - 1939-1940 Season
        - Candida, October 6-7, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Four New York State Plays (Plain Folks; York State Mill Town; Honeymoon-Niagara Falls; Fishin' Weather), October 27-28, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Ten Nights in a Bar-Room, November 3-4, 10-11, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Three One-Act Plays (Second Mortgage; Rehearsal; Simon Simon), December 1-2, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Hay Fever, December 12, 1939; Produced with Kastalia of Wells College (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Three New York State Plays (Yankee Makes a Bargain; Nothing Doing; Chenango Crone), December 15-16, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Four Comedies by Robert E. Gard (Strangers Rest Here; The Slope of a Hill; Raisin' th' Devil; Mixin' Up th' Rent, January 19-20, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Kind Lady, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
          Includes January 26-27 and February 9-10
        - Community Dramatics Festival: The Managers; The Will; Smile for the Lady; Sparkin', February 14, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - The Kermis Club: Raising the Devil; The Other Road; Sparkin'; Mixin' Up The Rent, Febuary 16, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - What a Life, March 8-9, 11, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Four Comedies (Marriage Proposal, Country Slicker, Box and Cox, Madge), March 14, 16, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Four Plays (There's Always Tomorrow; Get Out of Your Cage; Star Struck; In The Suds), April 12-13, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Heermans Prize Plays of 1940 (Domestic Relations; The Ripple; Over Fourteen, and Single; Chenango Crone), April 19-20, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Our Town, May 3-4, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Under the Gaslight, May 23-25, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
        - Accent on Youth, June 14-15, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 46)
      - Summer 1940
        - Our Town, July 12-13, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 47)
        - Four One-Act Plays (Star-Struck; The Hungerers; Budge, Budge Not; Overruled), July 26-27, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 47)
        - What a Life, August 2-3, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 47)
        - The Lake Guns of Seneca and Cayuga, August 9-10, 13-14, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 47)
      - 1940-1941 Season
        - Music Hall Show, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Springtime for Henry, November 8-9, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Three One Act Plays (The Women Folks and Their Man; A Night in the Country; Alma Mater), November 29-30, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - The Star-Wagon, December 13-14, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Three One-Act Plays (Red and Yellow; Minnie Field; Evening Dress Indispensable), January 17, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - My Heart's in the Highlands, February 7-8, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - The Chief Thing, March 7-8, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Three One-Act Plays (Close That Book; Gas and Electric; Crabbed Youth and Age), March 14, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - George and Margaret, March 21-22, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Heermans Prize Plays of 1941 (The Fork in the Road; McSorley; Cowboy Claudius Smith); No Matter What, April 25-26, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Music Hall Show, May 16-17, 23, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Wild Hills, May 24, 31, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - Beano, May 28, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
        - The Male Animal, June 13-14, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 48)
      - Summer 1941
        - Candida, July 11-12, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 49)
        - Wild Hills, July 19, 26, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 49)
        - The Male Animal, August 1-2, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 49)
        - Ladies in Retirement, August 8-9, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 49)
        - Four One-Act Plays (The Hope Chest; Hat and Stick; The Power of Fate; Crackerbarrel Joe), August 12, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 49)
      - 1941-1942 Season
        - The Lake Guns of Seneca and Cayuga, September 19, 1941; Produced by Cornell University and Hobart College Theatres (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - The Male Animal, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 50)
          Includes October 24-25 and November 7-8
        - Ladies in Retirement, November 14-15, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Three Cornell Plays (As Good as She is Beautiful; Mr. Swizzle Reads a Story; Forty-Four Proof), November 28, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Kerims: Cash on Hand; A Day in the VineYard; Crackerbarrel Joe; Devil's in the Pig Pen, December 5-6, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Three New York State Plays (John Brown Plants a Seed of Freedom; Flight from Connecticut Hill; The Bath at Cayuga Bridge), December 12-13, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Across the Continent, January 9-10, 16-17, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Jim Dandy, February 6-7, 1942; Laboratory Theatre (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Community Dramatics Festival: Mother Says Her Say; Crackerbarrel Joe; Devil's in the Pig Pen; The Dear Departed, February 11, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Three New York State Plays (Mr. Swizzle Reads a Story; A Day in the Vineyard; John Brown Plants a Seed of Freedom), February 12, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Jim Dandy, March 6-7, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 50)
        - Headin' for Havana, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 50)
          Includes March 13-14 and April 24-25
        - Thunder Rock, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 50)
          Includes March 20-21 and April 17-18
        - Love in '76, May 1-2, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 50)
      - Summer 1942
        - Jim Dandy, July 3-4, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 51)
        - Morning's at Seven, July 17-18, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 51)
        - Private Lives, July 24-25, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 51)
        - Thunder Rock, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 51)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (A Girl for the Hall; The Happy Journey to Camden and Trenton; The Theatre of the Soul; Moses, Saroyan and Welles), August 4-5, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 51)
        - Films Cornell Summer Theatre, July 7-28, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 51)
      - 1942-1943 Season
        - The Theatre of the Soul; The Happy Journey to Camden and Trenton; The Power of Fate; Moses, Saroyan and Welles, November 7, 1942; A theatre wing benefit for the entertainment fund for the Army and Navy (Box 43A, Folder 52)
        - No Mother to Guide Her, 1942 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
          Includes November 20-21 and December 4-5
        - Brief Music, 1942, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
          Includes December 12, 1942; January 8-9, 1943
        - Saroyan's Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning; The Hungerers; Fancy Free, January 16, 30, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
        - Three Experimental One-Act Plays (Monday; The Hope Chest; Pullman Car Hiawatha), February 19-20, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
        - The Music Hall Show, March 5-6, 12-13, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
        - Beyond the Horizon, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
          Includes March 20 and April 16-17
        - A Program of Comedy and Farce (Hullabaloo; Pyramus and Thisbe; A Man Should Have a Wife), May 7-8, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
        - A Private Performance of Three One-Act Plays (Overruled; They Refuse to be Resurrected; The Soul of a Professor), May 11-12, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 52)
      - Summer 1943
        - A Program of One-Act Plays(Hullabaloo; Overruled; Pyramus and Thisbe), July 9-10, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 53)
        - Beyond the Horizon, July 23-24, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 53)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (The Shadow Passes; A Seat in the Park; I'm a Fool; Lucy, the Farmer's Daughter), July 30-31, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 53)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (A Girl in Every Port; The Man in the Bowler Hat; Nell of the Golden West!), 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 53)
          Includes August 28 and September 4
        - Springtime for Henry, September 10-11, 17-18, 25, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 53)
      - 1943-1944 Season
        - Springtime for Henry, November 19-20, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (Star-Struck; The Pot Boiler; All on a Summer's Day; Hello Out There), December 3-4, 1943 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (Village Wooing; A Matter of Husbands; Fumed Oak), 1943, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
          Includes December 18, 1943; January 7-8, 1944
        - Nine Girls, January 21-22, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (John Doe; Why I am a Bachelor; The Happy Journey to Camden and Trenton), February 11-12, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - Nine Girls, March 11, 18, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - Anatol, April 15, 21-22, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - Four One-Act Plays (I'm a Fool; All on a Summer's Day; The Happy Journey to Camden and Trenton; Lucy, the Farmer's Daughter), April 28, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (At Liberty; Love and How to Cure It; I'm a Fool; Pyramus and Thisbe), May 6, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (I'm a Fool; All on a Summer's Day; Lucy, the Farmer's Daughter; The Happy Journey to Camden and Trenton; Pyramus and Thisbe), May 13, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
        - Our Town, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 54)
          Includes May 26-27 and June 9-10
      - Summer 1944
        - Our Town, July 8, 15, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 55)
        - Springtime for Henry, July 28-29, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 55)
        - A Program of One-Act Plays (The Hope Chest; Materia Medica; Murder is Fun!), August 4-5, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 55)
      - 1944-1945 Season
        - Plays of Three Nations (Sunday Costs Five Pesos; Evening Dress Indispensable; Hello Out There), October 7, 14, 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
        - Three One-Act Plays (Murder is Fun!; Evening Dress Indispensable; Hello Out There), 1944 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
          Includes November 25 and December 2
        - Four One-Act Plays (How He Lied to Her Husband; Mild Oats; Such Things Only Happen in Books; Quiet-Facing the Park), 1944, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
          Includes December 30, 1944; January 13, 1945
        - The Beautiful People, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
          Includes January 27; February 3, 10; March 17
        - Five One-Act Plays (Little Immortal; Overtones; The Power of Fate; Sparkin'; The Square Triangle), March 31, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
        - Four One-Act Plays (Overtones; The Power of Fate; Sparkin' The Square Triangle), April 10, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
        - John Gabriel Borkman, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
          Includes April 21 and May 4-5
        - Four One-Act Plays (Some Women Were Talking; The Bridegroom Waits; The Odd Streak; Lonesome-Like), May 12, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
        - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 56)
          Includes May 26 and June 1, 8-9
      - Summer 1945 (22nd)
        - The Skin of Our Teeth, July 6-7, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 57)
        - John Gabriel Borkman, July 14, 21, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 57)
        - Four One-Act Plays (Hello Out There; All on a Summer's Day; Mild Oats; The Power of Fate), July 27-28, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 57)
        - Four One-Act Plays (Hat and Stick; Some Women were Talking; Everybody's Husband; The Pot Boiler), August 4, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 57)
        - The Beautiful People, August 8-9, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 57)
      - 1945-1946 Season
        - The Pot Boiler, November 3, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
        - The Beautiful People, November 10, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
        - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
          Includes November 20, 24 and December 7-8
        - Three One-Act Period Plays (Box and Cox, Married and Settled; The Choir Rehearsal; Exile), December 14-15, 1945 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
        - Three One-Act Plays (Shall We Join the Ladies?; Travelling Light; Fancy Free), 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
          Includes January 26 and February 2, 9
        - Outward Bound, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
          Includes March 15-16, 23 and April 6
        - Three One-Act Plays (Pullman Car Hiawatha; Idyl on a Summer Hotel Porch; Two Gentleman of Soho), April 12-13, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
        - Once Upon a Hill, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 58)
          Includes April 19-20 and May 17-18
        - Two Gentleman of Soho, May 16, 1946; Performance for the Veterans' Wives Committee of Willard Straight Hall (Box 43A, Folder 58)
        - Six Characters in Search of an Author; The Beautiful People; Pullman Car Hiawatha, 1946; Laboratory Theatre (Box 43A, Folder 58)
          Includes May 31 and June 1
      - Summer 1946
        - The Beautiful People, July 5-6, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 59)
        - Outward Bound, July 12-13, 20, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 59)
        - Four One-Act Plays (Fumed Oak; They Refuse to be Resurrected; Etiquette; A Pound on Demand), July 26-27, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 59)
        - The Damask Cheek, August 2-3, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 59)
      - 1946-1947 Season
        - Yankee Land, October 12, 1946; Presented at the 44th Annual Meeting of the New York State Historical Association (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - The Pot Boiler, October 14, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Yankee Land, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
          Includes October 18-19 and November 1-2
        - Damask Cheek, November 20-23, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - R.U.R. (Rossum's Universal Robots), December 4-7, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - The Second Shepherds' Play, December 14, 1946 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning, January 18, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Across the Board on Tomorrow Morning; Hands Across the Sea, February 14-15, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Riders to the Sea; The Intruder; Wurzel-Flummery, March 14-15, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Fanny's First Play, March 27-29, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - The Pigeon, April 24-26, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Ah, Wilderness!, May 9-10, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Heermans Prize Plays (While the Moon Grows Cold; Fair Day Thursday; The Woman in Bed), May 23-24, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
        - Ah, Wilderness!, June 13-14, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 60)
      - Summer 1947
        - The Pigeon, July 11-12, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 61)
        - On Approval, July 18-19, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 61)
        - An Evening of One Act Plays (Star-Struck; Overruled; In the Suds), July 25-26, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 61)
        - Ah, Wilderness!, August 1-2, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 61)
      - 1947-1948 Season
        - In the Suds, September 20, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - On Approval, October 3-4, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - Joan of Lorraine, November 6-8, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - An Evening of One Act Plays (Ile; A Seat in the Park; Lord Byron's Love Letter; The Happy Journey), November 21-22, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - Alison's House, December 4-6, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - The Second Shepherds' Play, December 13, 1947 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - Blithe Spirit, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
          Includes January 15-17 and February 6-7
        - The Philadelphia Story, March 4-6, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - The Doctor in Spite of Himself, April 22-24, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - An Evening of One Act Plays (No Matter What; Kate and her Horns; Black Velvet; Her Heart was Richer than Gold), May 7-8, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
        - Night Must Fall, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 62)
          Includes May 21-22 and June 11-12
      - Summer 1948 (25th)
        - The Doctor in Spite of Himself, July 16-17, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 63)
        - Springtime for Henry, July 23-24, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 63)
        - An Evening of One Act Plays (Lord Byron's Love Letter; The Happy Journey; A Seat in the Park; Her Heart Was Richer Than Gold), July 30-31, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 63)
        - Ladies in Retirement, August 6-7, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 63)
      - 1948-1949 Season (40th)
        - Her Heart Was Richer than Gold, September 18, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - You Touched Me!, October 21-23, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - The Barretts of Wimpole Street, October 30, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - You Touched Me!, November 5-6, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - An Evening of One Act Plays (Champeen of the Canawl; Portrait of a Madonna; The Cocklepfiefer Case), November 19, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - Arsenic and Old Lace, December 2-4, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - The Second Shepherds' Play, December 11, 1948 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - Macbeth, February 4-5, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - An Inspector Calls, March 17-19, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - The Ascent of F6, April 14-16, 1949; Laboratory Players (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - Deep are the Roots, April 28-30, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
        - Boy Meets Girl, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 64)
          Includes May 20-21 and June 11-12
        - Cornell Dramatic Club Annual Letter to Former Members Season 1948-1949 40th Season (Box 43A, Folder 64)
      - Summer 1949
        - The Little Foxes, July 7-9, 1949; Ithaca Community Players (Box 43A, Folder 65)
        - The Ascent of F6, July 15-16, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 65)
        - Mr. Pim Passes By, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 65)
          Includes July 22-23, September 30 and October 1
        - An Evening of One Act Plays (That's Hollywood; Papa Never Done Nothing... Much; Mooney's Kid Don't Cry; They Refuse to Be Resurrected), July 29-30, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 65)
        - The Vinegar Tree, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 65)
          August 5-6 and October 21-22
      - 1949-1950 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 18, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - The Winslow Boy, November 3-5, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - Three One-Act Plays (The General Retreats; Bath at Cayuga Bridge; Aria Da Capo), November 18, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - Beauty and the Beast, December 2-3, 1949; Performed by children from kindergarten-6th grades of the Fall Creek School (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - Happy Birthday, December 8-10, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - A Child Is Born, December 17, 1949 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - The Winslow Boy, December 17, 1949; Performed at Amherst Central High School under the auspices of the Cornell Clubs of Buffalo (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - As You Like It, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
          Includes January 13 and February 3-4
        - Box and Cox; Trial by Jury, March 3-4, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - Of Mice and Men, March 16-18, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - The Play's the Thing, April 20-22, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - Two Original One-Act Plays by Cornell Authors (Ticonderoga; For Modern Mummers), May 4, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - Dr. Knock, May 12-14, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
        - Two Blind Mice, June 9-11, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 66)
      - Summer 1950
        - They Knew What They Wanted, July 6-8, 1950; Ithaca Community Players (Box 43A, Folder 67)
        - The Play's the Thing, July 14-15, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 67)
        - Home and Beauty, July 21-22, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 67)
        - Cornell One-Act Plays (A Man Should Have a Wife; (Unnamed); Three Cheers for Woody), July 28-29, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 67)
        - Angel Street, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 67)
          Includes August 4-5 and October 20-21
      - 1950-1951 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 16, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - One Act Plays (A Man's Duty; (Unnamed); Three Cheers for Woody), November 3, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - Unpaved Roads; How He Lied to Her Husband, November 8, 1950; Actors' Lab Series (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - Arms and the Man, November 16-19, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - Once Upon a Hill, December 14-17, 1950 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - The Bonds of Interest, February 2-3, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - Summer and Smoke, February 22-25, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - H.M.S. Pinafore, March 7-10, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - Cornell One-Act Plays (The Cellar; Paul Invents Logging; The Tarnished; Business As Usual), March 16, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - The Wild Duck, April 19-22, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
        - The Taming of the Shrew, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 68)
          Includes May 11-13 and June 8-10
      - Summer 1951
        - The Silver Whistle, July 5-7, 1951; Ithaca Community Players (Box 43A, Folder 69)
        - The Wild Duck, July 13-14, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 69)
        - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 69)
        - One-Act Plays (Sincerely Yours, Cleopatra; The Soul of a Professor; A Phoenix Too Frequent), July 27-28, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 69)
        - The Detour, August 3-4, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 69)
      - 1951-1952 Season
        - Pyramus and Thisbe, September 15, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 70)
        - The Importance of Being Earnest, October 11-14, 1951 (Box 43A, Folder 70)